bedguru.co.uk 2014-12-03

# Privacy - The Bed Guru, Specialising in a Good Night's Sleep for Over 27 Years. The Bed Guru, Leeds.

The Bed Guru take the privacy of our website users very seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalised and valuable service. This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices of www.bedguru.co.uk If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail.

## Use of Cookies

We may use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the www.bedguru.co.uk website and to build up a demographic profile.

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser.

Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site.

### Information Collected

We collect personal information from you through the use of enquiry and registration forms and every time you e-mail us your details.

We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which inc demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form.

#### Use of Personal information

We process personal information collected via www.bedguru.co.uk for the purposes of:

  * providing a personalised service 
  * conducting market research surveys 
  * running promotions and
  * providing you with information about products and services we offer. 

We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified):

  * to build up marketing profiles
  * to aid strategic development 
  * to manage our relationship with advertisers and 
  * to audit usage of the site. 

##### Disclosures

We will not disclose any information we keep about you to any third parties, except for; credit reference agency clearance (where you have submitted a completed order form for goods or services), and any suppliers we engage to provide services which involve processing data on our behalf.

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the www.bedguru.co.uk website and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
